<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming: The Lean Scientist: Productivity in Science</title>
      <link>/docs/5_nick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/5_nick/</guid>
      <description>The Lean Scientist: Productivity in Science. -- Speaker: Nicholas A. Del Grosso
Date: 05 Feb 2019, 18:30 Location: TUM main campus, building N1, room N1135
 About our speaker: Nicholas A. Del Grosso, is a postdoctoral researcher in Proteomics, at the Max Planck Institute for Biochemistry. During his PhD, he designed and built a virtual reality system for freely-moving rodents in the Sirota Lab (Cognition and Neural Plasticity) at LMU. He is not only a passionate neuroscientist but also a professional Pythonista, having written several high- and low-level Python libraries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Microelectrode Arrays</title>
      <link>/docs/4_lennard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/4_lennard/</guid>
      <description>Flexible Microelectrode Arrays. -- Speakers: Lennard de Graaf, Francisco Zurita Date: 14 Jan 2019, 18:30 Location: Karlsraße 45   The talk was divided in two parts presented to us by our fellow MSNE students: 
1. Histological evaluation of flexible neural implants; flexibility limit for reducing the tissue response? Lee, et al.  by Lennard de Graaf

Background of our speakers: Lennard studies medicine at the Erasmus University Rotterdam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Image Processing Application</title>
      <link>/docs/3_fatemeh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/3_fatemeh/</guid>
      <description>Multimodal Image Processing Application. Date: 29.12.2018   Our recent talk happened on the 29th of November. We had a pleasure of hosting Fatemeh Nejatbakhsh, who was a recent a Visiting Researcher at Columbia University (where she worked with Prof. Gregory C Sharp) and is a PhD candidate at Department of Neurology of Ludwig-Maximilian Universität in Munich. Our speakers interest consists of developing medical devices but also methods for biomedical image processing, she is also passionate about: vestibular system, brain imaging and cognitive studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Temporal Memory</title>
      <link>/docs/2_connor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/2_connor/</guid>
      <description>Hierarchical Temporal Memory given by Connor Leahy. Date: 7.11.2018
 On 7th of November we had the pleasure to host our first guest of the winter semester - Connor Leahy. Connor is a passionate Computer Science student at TUM. Most of his knowledge is self-taught, in his free time he loves reading about Machine Learning, Neuroscience, Statistics, and Philosophy. He has recently started working at Max Planck Institute of Psychiatry, where he is developing a system to automatically detect dendritic spines with images from two-photon microscopy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear from the Heart</title>
      <link>/docs/1_werner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/1_werner/</guid>
      <description>First Talk Behind Us!  On 25 of June one of the MSNE Students gave the first official talk for our Journal Club:
Topic: &amp;ldquo;Fear from the Heart: Sensitivity to Fear Stimuli Depends on Individual Heartbeats&amp;rdquo;, Garfinkel et al.
Speaker: Werner Seitz   First talk by Werner Seitz   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>