<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming: Multimodal Image Processing Application</title>
      <link>/docs/3_fatemeh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/3_fatemeh/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming talk: Multimodal Image Processing Application. Date: 29.12.2018 at 19:00 , doors open at 18.30 Place: Karlstr. 45, room 2026 - ICS Seminar Room
  Upcoming talk will be presented by Fatemeh Nejatbakhsh. She will talk about image processing in medical applications. Starting with the basic concepts, she is going to explain the typical steps of a processing pipeline. After a general overview we will dive into detailed applications. Special attention will be given to the implications of conceptually establishing a design, as it is needed in administrative positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Temporal Memory</title>
      <link>/docs/2_connor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/2_connor/</guid>
      <description>Hierarchical Temporal Memory given by Connor Leahy. Date: 7.11.2018
  On 7th of November we had the pleasure to host our first guest of the winter semester - Connor Leahy. Connor is a passionate Computer Science student at TUM. Most of his knowledge is self-taught, in his free time he loves reading about Machine Learning, Neuroscience, Statistics, and Philosophy. He has recently started working at Max Planck Institute of Psychiatry, where he is developing a system to automatically detect dendritic spines with images from two-photon microscopy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear from the Heart</title>
      <link>/docs/1_werner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/1_werner/</guid>
      <description>First Talk Behind Us!  On 25 of June one of the MSNE Students gave the first official talk for our Journal Club:
Topic: &amp;ldquo;Fear from the Heart: Sensitivity to Fear Stimuli Depends on Individual Heartbeats&amp;rdquo;, Garfinkel et al.
Speaker: Werner Seitz   First talk by Werner Seitz   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>